Guide to the Albrecht Goetze Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Inventory, 1923-1971; 8.25; (22 boxes)
  - Birkeland, Harris, 1946, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Birot, Maurice(*), 1952-1964 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Bittel, Kurt(*), 1932-1939, 1949-1963 (Box 3, Folder 72-75)
  - Bittel, Kurt, 1964-1970, undated (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Blake, Frank Ringgold, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Blake, Robert P., 1936, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Blinkenberg, Christian S., 1934 (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Bloch, Bernard, 1940-1941, 1952-1953, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 77)
    See also: box 9, folder 215
  - Bloch, S.J., 1942 (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Boardman, John, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Bodmer-Gessner, Verena, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Böhl, Franz M.T.(*), 1929, 1933-1934, 1946-1959 (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Boehringer, Erich, 1963, undated (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Böker, Robert, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Boer, E., 1966 (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Boissier, Alfred, 1930-1936 (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Bonfante, Giuliano, 1940-1947, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Bonner, Campbell, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Books for the Colleges of Denmark, undated (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Borger, Riekele(*), 1961-1970 (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Bork, Ferdinand, 1926-1927, 1936 (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - Borowski, Elie, 1946-1950 (Box 3, Folder 80)
    See also: box 7, folder 156-157
  - Bossert, Helmuth Th.(*), 1932-1936, 1942, 1949-1961 (Box 4, Folder 81)
    See also: box 2, folder 28-50 See also: box 20, folder 525
  - Boston, Museum of Fine Arts, 1959-1961 (Box 4, Folder 81)
  - Bothmer, Bernard
    See: box 3, folder 80
  - Bottéro, Jean(*), 1948-1967, undated (Box 4, Folder 82-83)
  - Bouda, Karl, 1946-1947 (Box 4, Folder 84)
  - Bouley, Frank, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 84)
  - Boyce, Mary, 1955, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 84)
    See also: box 5, folder 107
  - Boyer, Georges, 1946, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 84)
  - Braidwood, Linda (Mrs. Robert), 1953-1955, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 84)
  - Braidwood, Robert(*), 1944, 1948-1961 (Box 4, Folder 85)
    See also: box 2, folder 28-50
  - Brand, Karl, 1935 (Box 4, Folder 86)
  - Brandenstein, Wilhelm, 1937-1939, 1946-1947, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 86)
  - Braun, Gustav, 1933-1937 (Box 4, Folder 86)
  - Bravmann, Meir Moshe, 1947, 1953, 1955, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 86)
  - Breasted, James H., 1933-1934 (Box 4, Folder 86)
  - Brendel, Otto, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 86)
  - Briggs, Robert E., 1949 (Box 4, Folder 87)
  - Brill, E.J., 1937-1940, 1954-1958, 1965-1967 (Box 4, Folder 87)
  - Brilliant, Richard, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 87)
  - Brinkman, John A., 1962-1964, 1971, undated (Box 4, Folder 87)
  - British Institute of Archaeology at Ankara, 1953-1960 (Box 4, Folder 87)
    See also box 12, folder 304
  - British Museum, 1931-1932, 1960-1961, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 87)
    See also: box 3, folder 62 See also: box 7, folder 170-171 See also: box 18, folder 484 See also: box 20, folder 541-543
  - British School of Archaeology in Iraq, 1954-1969 (Box 4, Folder 87)
  - Brooklyn Museum, 1953-1954 (Box 4, Folder 88)
  - Brooks, William E., 1949, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 88)
  - Brown, A. F. R., 1952 (Box 4, Folder 88)
  - Brown, Darrell L., 1962 (Box 4, Folder 88)
  - Brown, William Norman
    See: box 1, folder 17 See: box 10, folder 239-247
  - Brownstein, Nathan, 1940 (Box 4, Folder 89)
  - Bryn Mawr College, 1936-1937, 1968-1970 (Box 4, Folder 89)
  - Buccellati, Giorgio, 1960-1964 (Box 4, Folder 89)
  - Buchanan, Briggs(*), 1947-1957, undated (Box 4, Folder 90)
  - Buchanan, Harvey, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 90)
  - Buckler, William H., undated (Box 4, Folder 91)
  - Buddhaprakash, ____, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 91)
  - Bull, Ludlow, 1936, 1940, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 91)
  - Bunnell, LeRoy, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 91)
  - Bunte, Wolfgang, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 91)
  - Burrage, Champlin, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 91)
  - Burrows, Millar(*), 1936-1942 (Box 4, Folder 92)
  - Burrows, Millar(*), 1943-1948, 1953, 1957-1961, undated (Box 4, Folder 93)
  - CBS News, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 94)
  - Cabinet Royale de Medailles, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 94)
  - Cadbury, Henry J., undated (Box 4, Folder 94)
  - Caldwell, Wallace, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 94)
  - California, University of, 1953-1956 (Box 4, Folder 94)
  - Calmeyer, Peter, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 94)
  - Cambel, Halet, 1948, 1954, 1956, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 94)
  - Cambridge Ancient History, 1951-1954 (Box 4, Folder 94)
    See also: box 4, folder 95 See also: box 7, folder 170-171
  - Cambridge University Press, 1953, 1961-1965, 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 95)
  - Cameron, George G.(*), 1946-1958 (Box 4, Folder 96)
  - Cameron, George G.(*), 1959-1970 (Box 4, Folder 97)
  - Canby, Jeanny E. Vorys (Mrs. Thomas Y., Jr.)(*), 1955-1965, 1971, n.d (Box 4, Folder 98)
  - Cannon, William R., 1953 (Box 4, Folder 98)
  - Capelle, Wilhelm, 1925 (Box 4, Folder 99)
  - Cardascia, Guillaume, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 99)
  - Carlson, E. Leslie, 1947-1949 (Box 4, Folder 99)
  - Carr, Iris C. (Mrs. Herman E., Jr.), undated (Box 4, Folder 99)
  - Carter, Charles, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 99)
  - Carter, Theresa H., 1967 (Box 4, Folder 99)
  - Casey, Robert, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 99)
  - Castellino, Giorgio Raffaele, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 99)
  - Catholic University of America, 1953, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 99)
  - Cavaignac, Eugene, 1946, 1950, undated (Box 4, Folder 99)
  - Cazelles, Henri, 1955, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 100)
  - Center for Applied Linguistics, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 100)
  - Centre International de Synthèse, Institut International d'Archéocivilisation, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 100)
  - Chadwick, John, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 100)
  - Chafe, Wallace L., undated (Box 4, Folder 101)
  - Chandler, Tertius, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 101)
  - Chao, Yuen Ren, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 101)
  - Chicago, University of, Press(*), 1945, 1961-1970 (Box 4, Folder 101)
  - Chiera, Edward, 1931 (Box 4, Folder 101)
  - Childe, V. Gordon, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 101)
  - Christensen, Arthur M., 1933-1939 (Box 4, Folder 102)
  - Christian, Viktor, 1928-1930, 1960-1961 (Box 4, Folder 102)
  - Christoph, D.H., 1949 (Box 4, Folder 102)
  - Cincinnati Art Museum, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 102)
  - Civil, Michel, 1959-1965 (Box 4, Folder 103)
  - Clairmont, Christoph, 1960-1961 (Box 4, Folder 103)
  - Clark, Walter E., 1946, 1950-1951 (Box 4, Folder 103)
  - Clark, ____ (Mrs. H.P.), 1950 (Box 4, Folder 103)
  - Classical Weekly, 1937 (Box 4, Folder 103)
  - Cocco, Vincenso, 1940 (Box 4, Folder 103)
  - Cohen, Isaac, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 103)
  - Cohen, Marcel, 1940 (Box 4, Folder 103)
  - Collège de France, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 103)
  - Columbia University, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 103)
  - Columbia University Libraries, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 103)
  - Conference on the Literary Heritage of the Near East, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 104)
  - Conn, George H., 1961 (Box 4, Folder 104)
  - Connecticut Academy of Arts and Sciences, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 104)
  - Conseil International de la Philosophie et des Sciences Humaines, 1959,1965 (Box 4, Folder 104)
  - Coppens, Joseph, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 105)
  - Cornelius, Friedrich(*), 1955-1960, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 105)
  - Cornell University, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 105)
  - Cornell University Library, 1946, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 105)
  - Cornwall, Peter B.(*), 1947, 1951-1953 (Box 4, Folder 106)
  - Corpus Inscriptionum Iranicarum, 1957-1963, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 107)
  - Coues, Charlotte O. (Mrs. Robert), 1950 (Box 5, Folder 108)
  - Courant, R., 1935, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 108)
  - Courtney, Denis A., 1946 (Box 5, Folder 108)
  - Couvreur, Walter, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 108)
  - Cowan, J. Milton
    See: box 13, folder 338-343
  - Cox, Gordon E., 1948 (Box 5, Folder 109)
  - Crawford, Vaughn E.(*), 1949-1957 (Box 5, Folder 109)
  - Crawford, Vaughn E.(*), 1958-1967 (Box 5, Folder 110)
  - Cross, Dorothy, 1936-1937 (Box 5, Folder 111)
  - Cross, Ephraim, 1936-1937, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 111)
  - Cross, Frank M., Jr., 1956-1960, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 111)
  - Crossland, Ronald A.(*), 1946-1956 (Box 5, Folder 112-113)
  - Crossland, Ronald A., 1957-1960, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 114)
  - Crozer Quarterly, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 114)
  - Crozer Theological Seminary, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 114)
  - Cuny, Albert L.M., [pre-1930?] (Box 5, Folder 114)
  - Current Anthropology, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 115)
  - Curtius, Ludwig, 1928, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 115)
  - Dahood, Mitchell, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 115)
  - Dale, B.J., 1933 (Box 5, Folder 115)
  - Dales, George F., 1959-1963 (Box 5, Folder 115)
  - Dalglish, Edward R., 1965, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 115)
  - Danaher, John A., 1941 (Box 5, Folder 115)
  - Danmanville, Jenny, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 115)
  - Danske Videnskabernes Selskab, 1938-1939 (Box 5, Folder 115)
  - David, E.S., 1963 (Box 5, Folder 115)
  - David, Martin(*), 1934-1940, 1947-1954 (Box 5, Folder 116)
  - Davidson, Adelaide M., 1936-1940 (Box 5, Folder 117)
  - Dawn, Ernest, 1942, 1946, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 117)
  - Debrunner, Albert, 1926, 1932, 1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 117)
  - Deeters, Gerhard, 1932-1933, 1936 (Box 5, Folder 117)
  - Deimel, [P.] Anton(*), 1929-1937, 1946-1951 (Box 5, Folder 118)
  - Delanghe, Robert, 1947 (Box 6, Folder 119)
  - Delaporte, Louis Joseph(*), 1928-1932 (Box 6, Folder 119)
  - Delougaz, Pinhas, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 119)
  - Demircioğlu, Halil, undated (Box 6, Folder 120)
  - Demorest, Charles, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 120)
  - Dentan, Robert C., 1960 (Box 6, Folder 120)
  - Denver Art Museum, 1963-1966 (Box 6, Folder 120)
  - Detweiler, Albert Henry
  - Deutsche Akademie für Sprache und Dichtung, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 120)
  - Deutsche Orient-Gesellschaft, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 120)
  - Deutsches Archäologisches Institut, 1963-1966 (Box 6, Folder 121)
  - Deutsches Institut für Aegyptische Altertumskunde, 1929 (Box 6, Folder 121)
  - Devoto, Giacomo, 1925, 1934-1938, undated (Box 6, Folder 121)
  - Dhorme, Edouard(*), 1946-1952, 1957-1960 (Box 6, Folder 122)
  - Diakanoff, ____, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 123)
  - Dietrich, A[lbert?], 1956 (Box 6, Folder 123)
  - Diez, Ernst, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 123)
  - Dihle, Albrecht, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 123)
  - Dijk, Johannes Jacobus Adrianus van, 1960-1965 (Box 6, Folder 123)
  - Dikaios, Porphyrios, 1952-1956, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 123)
  - Dillon, John M., 1962-1963 (Box 6, Folder 123)
  - Dillon, Myles(*), 1942-1947, 1954-1955, 1961-1963, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 124)
  - Directory of American Scholars, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 124)
  - Dönmez, Ahmet, 1956-1957 (Box 6, Folder 125)
  - Döner, F.K.
    See: box 3, folder 52-53
  - Donner, Fred M., 1967 (Box 6, Folder 125)
  - Dossin, Georges, 1934, 1938-1940, 1946-1957 (Box 6, Folder 125)
  - Dovener, M., 1951 (Box 6, Folder 125)
  - Downing, Arthur, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 126)
  - Draffkorn, Anne
    See: box 11, folder 277
  - Draicchio, Maureen, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 126)
  - Drinker, Sophie M. (Mrs. Henry S.), 1953 (Box 6, Folder 126)
  - Drioton, Etienne
    See: box 20, folder 528
  - Dritz, Arthur, undated (Box 6, Folder 126)
  - Driver, Godfrey Rolles, 1938-1940, 1946-1956, 1962, undated (Box 6, Folder 127)
  - Drohla, Wolfgang, 1933-1939, undated (Box 6, Folder 127)
  - Duchesne-Guillemin, Marcelle, 1963-1964 (Box 6, Folder 128)
  - [Düner?], Friedrich Karl, 1954 (Box 6, Folder 128)
  - Dugat, Gentry, 1952-1955 (Box 6, Folder 128)
  - Dunajevskaja, Irina, undated (Box 6, Folder 128)
  - Dyggve, Ejnar, 1935-1936 (Box 6, Folder 128)
  - Dyson, Robert H., Jr., 1959-1963 (Box 6, Folder 128)
  - Ebeling, Erich, 1927-1934, 1950-1955 (Box 6, Folder 129)
  - Edel, Elmar(*), 1947-1951, 1957-1958, 1964-1967 (Box 6, Folder 130)
  - Edelstein, Ludwig, 1937-1938, 1957-1959 (Box 6, Folder 131)
  - Edgerton, Franklin, 1934, 1939-1941, 1953, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 131)
  - Edgerton, William F., 1935, 1940, 1942 (Box 6, Folder 132)
  - Edhem, Halil, 1925-1931 (Box 6, Folder 132)
  - Edzard, Dietz O.(*), 1956-1963, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 132)
  - èfrat, E. Ğ.
    See: box 7, folder 174
  - Ege, Niels, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 132)
  - Ehelolf, Hans(*), 1924-1932 (Box 6, Folder 133-136)
  - Ehelolf, Hans, 1933-1938 (Box 6, Folder 137)
  - Ehelolf, Luise (Mrs. Hans), 1947-1951, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 138)
  - Ehrenberg, Victor, 1925, 1928, 1936-1938 (Box 6, Folder 138)
  - Ehrenfeld, Adolf, 1938 (Box 6, Folder 139)
  - Ehrenkreutz, Andrew S., 1954 (Box 6, Folder 139)
  - Ehrich, Ann M.H., 1939 (Box 6, Folder 139)
  - Eilers, Wilhelm, 1952-1953 (Box 6, Folder 139)
  - Einersen, Jean, 1934, undated (Box 6, Folder 140)
  - Eisler, Robert, 1925 (Box 6, Folder 140)
  - Eissfeldt, Otto, 1957, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 140)
  - El-Amin, Mahmud
  - Elbogen, Ismar, 1940 (Box 6, Folder 140)
  - "Elephant"
    See: box 15, folder 373-379
  - Ellis, Maria (Mrs. R.S.), 1967 (Box 6, Folder 140)
  - Encyclopedia Britannica, 1938, 1958, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 141)
  - Encyclopedia Hebraica, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 141)
  - Engberg, Robert M., 1942, 1947 (Box 6, Folder 141)
  - Ephron, Henry D., 1959 (Box 6, Folder 142)
  - Epstein, Claire, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 142)
  - Evans, Geoffrey, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 142)
  - Ewen, Patricia, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 142)
  - Fabricius, Knud, 1930 (Box 6, Folder 142)
  - Falkenstein, Adam(*), 1950-1966 (Box 6, Folder 143-144)
  - Farber, Eduard, 1946-1949 (Box 6, Folder 145)
  - Faust, David Earl, 1941 (Box 6, Folder 145)
  - Federn, Walter, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 145)
  - Feigin, Samuel I.(*), 1934-1946 (Box 6, Folder 145)
  - Feist, Ilse
    See: box 11, folder 271
  - Ferm, Vergilius, 1947 (Box 6, Folder 146)
  - Fiesel, Eva, 1934-1937 (Box 6, Folder 146)
    See also: box 4, folder 89 See also: box 4, folder 103
  - Figulla, Hugo Heinrich, 1939, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 146)
  - Fimmen, Walther, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 146)
  - Finet, André, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 146)
  - Finkelscherer Bruno, 1938 (Box 6, Folder 146)
  - Finkelstein, Dorothée (Mrs. Jacob J.), 1964 (Box 6, Folder 146)
  - Finkelstein, Jacob J.(*), 1953-1965 (Box 6, Folder 147-152)
  - Fischer, Franz, 1956-1957, 1965-1966 (Box 6, Folder 153)
  - Fischer, Henry, 1954-1955, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 153)
  - Fish, Thomas, 1946-1951 (Box 6, Folder 153)
  - Flora, Delbert B., 1954 (Box 6, Folder 154)
  - Follin, Maynard D., 1940 (Box 6, Folder 154)
  - Ford, Michael, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 154)
  - Forrer, Emil, 1925, 1937 (Box 6, Folder 154)
  - Fossey, Charles, 1938, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 154)
  - Fraenkel, Ruth (Mrs.Eduard), 1937 (Box 6, Folder 154)
  - Frank, Erich, 1934, 1946-1947 (Box 7, Folder 155)
  - Frankel, Hermann, 1935 (Box 7, Folder 155)
  - Frankfort, Henri(*), 1930-1936, 1940-1948 (Box 7, Folder 156-157)
  - Frankfort, Henri(*), 1949-1954 (Box 7, Folder 158)
  - Frankfort, ____ (Mrs. Henri), undated (Box 7, Folder 158)
  - Frankfurter, Felix, 1937 (Box 7, Folder 159)
  - Freemark, Ernest, 1951-1952 (Box 7, Folder 159)
  - Freiburg, Universität, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 159)
  - Friedländer, Paul, 1938-1940 (Box 7, Folder 159)
  - Friedrich, Johannes(*), 1924-1928 (Box 7, Folder 160-161)
  - Friedrich, Johannes, 1929-1930 (Box 7, Folder 162)
  - Friedrich, Johannes(*), 1931-1941, 1945-1957, 1968, undated (Box 7, Folder 163-167)
  - Fries, Charles C., 1938 (Box 7, Folder 168)
  - Frisch, Charles F., 1942, 1946 (Box 7, Folder 168)
  - Fritz, Kurt von, [post-1934] (Box 7, Folder 168)
  - Frye, Richard N., 1946-1947, 1950, 1954 (Box 7, Folder 168)
  - Fuchs, Marcus
    See: box 8, folder 192
  - Fulton, John F., 1940, 1955, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 168)
  - Furlani, Giuseppe, 1946 (Box 7, Folder 168)
  - Furniss, Edgar S., 1939 (Box 7, Folder 168)
  - Gabbrielli, Luciana, 1945,1949-1951 (Box 7, Folder 169)
  - Gadd, Cyril J.(*), 1930-1938, 1946-1968 (Box 7, Folder 170-171)
  - Galling, Kurt, 1929 (Box 7, Folder 172)
  - Gamkrelidze, Th., 1961 (Box 7, Folder 172)
  - Gardin, Jean Claude, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 172)
  - Gardner, Dillard S., 1950 (Box 7, Folder 172)
  - Gardner, Grandison, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 172)
  - Garelli, Paul, 1958-1967 (Box 7, Folder 172)
  - Garra, Richard, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 173)
  - Garstang, John(*), 1929-1946, undated (Box 7, Folder 173)
  - Gaster, Moses, 1924 (Box 7, Folder 173)
  - Gaster, Theodor H., 1940, 1947-1953, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 174)
  - Gaul, James H., 1938-1940 (Box 7, Folder 174)
  - Geddie, Henry L., 1963 (Box 7, Folder 174)
  - Geers, Frederick William, 1929-1930, 1944-1947, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 174)
  - Gehman, Henry S., 1950 (Box 7, Folder 175)
  - Geiger, Bernhard, 1938, 1942, 1946 (Box 7, Folder 175)
  - Geiger, Wilhelm, [pre-1931] (Box 7, Folder 175)
  - Gelb, Ignace J.(*), 1936, 1940-1943 1947-1968 (Box 7, Folder 176-177)
  - Georgacas, Demetrius J., 1947, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 178)
  - Georgetown University, School of Foreign Service, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 178)
  - Gese, Hartmut(*), 1953-1965 (Box 7, Folder 178)
  - Geuthner, Paul, 1938, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 179)
  - Gibson, McGuire, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 179)
  - Gilfillan, F.A., 1962 (Box 8, Folder 179)
  - Gillings, Richard J., 1953-1955, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 179)
  - Ginsberg, Harold L.(*), 1938-1943 (Box 8, Folder 179)
  - Ginzberg, Louis, 1938 (Box 8, Folder 180)
  - Gjerstad, Einar, 1935 (Box 8, Folder 180)
  - Gjødesen, Mogens, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 180)
  - Glazer, Sidney, 1936, 1946, undated (Box 8, Folder 180)
  - Gleye, Arthur, 1936 (Box 8, Folder 180)
  - Glidden, Harold W., 1938-1939 (Box 8, Folder 180)
  - Glueck, Nelson, 1937,1948,1951 (Box 8, Folder 180)
  - Gnomon, 1955,1957 (Box 8, Folder 180)
  - Goell, Theresa(*), 1948-1953 (Box 8, Folder 181)
  - Goell, Theresa(*), 1954-1959 (Box 8, Folder 182)
  - Götze, Hermann, 1931, 1949 (Box 8, Folder 182)
  - Goff, Beatrice, 1962, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 183)
  - Goitein, Solomon Dob Fritz, 1959-1970 (Box 8, Folder 183)
  - Goldin, J[udah?], 1958 (Box 8, Folder 183)
  - Goldman, Hetty(*), 1935-1936 (Box 8, Folder 183)
  - Goldman, Hetty(*), 1937-1939, 1944-1946 (Box 8, Folder 184)
  - Goldman, Hetty(*), 1948-1959 (Box 8, Folder 185)
  - Goldschmidt, ____, 1930 (Box 8, Folder 185)
  - Gomez, Emilio Garcia, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 186)
  - Goodenough, Cynthia G. (Mrs. Erwin R.), 1959 (Box 8, Folder 186)
  - Goodenough, Erwin R., 1936-1941, 1946-1955 (Box 8, Folder 186)
  - Goossens, Godfrey, 1938, 1946, 1949, 1953, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 187)
  - Gordon, Cyrus H.(*), 1934-1942, 1946-1952 (Box 8, Folder 188-189)
  - Gordon, Edmund I.(*), 1957-1961, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 190)
  - Gough, Mary (Mrs. Michael R.E.), 1955 (Box 8, Folder 191)
  - Gough, Michael R.E., 1961-1962 (Box 8, Folder 191)
  - Granberry, Julian M., 1951-1954 (Box 8, Folder 191)
  - Grant, Elihu, 1937-1938, undated (Box 8, Folder 191)
  - Grantier, B.J., 1958 (Box 8, Folder 191)
  - Grapow, Hermann, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 191)
  - Grayson, Albert Kirk, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 192)
  - Great Britain, Consulate General, Frankfort on the Main, 1928 (Box 8, Folder 192)
  - Greenberg, Joseph H., 1951 (Box 8, Folder 192)
  - Greenberg, Moshe, 1955, 1964-1965 (Box 8, Folder 192)
  - Greenfield, Jonas C., 1962, 1964, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 192)
  - Greengus, Samuel, 1965-1966 (Box 8, Folder 192)
  - Grégoire, Henri, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 193)
  - Grey, Louis H., 1942 (Box 8, Folder 193)
  - Griffin, Ralph W., 1953 (Box 8, Folder 193)
  - Griswold, A. Whitney, 1953-1954, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 193)
  - Grohmann, Adolf, 1926 (Box 8, Folder 193)
  - Group for Hamitic and Semitic Linguistics
    See: box 8, folder 179 See: box 14, folder 351
  - Gruenewald, Max, 1929, 1931, 1933-1940 (Box 8, Folder 193)
  - Güntert, Hermann, 1929 (Box 8, Folder 193)
  - Güterbock, Hans G.(*), 1931-1939, 1944-1946 (Box 8, Folder 194)
  - Güterbock, Hans G., 1947-1948 (Box 8, Folder 195)
  - Güterbock, Hans G.(*), 1949-1960 (Box 8, Folder 196-198)
  - Güterbock, Hans G.(*), 1961-1970 (Box 8, Folder 199)
  - Guggenheim Memorial Foundation, 1945, 1950-1958 (Box 8, Folder 200)
  - Gumbel, Emil Julius(*), 1933-1936, 1940-1943, [1946?], 1952, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 200)
  - Gumbel, Marieluise (Mrs. E. J.), [1940?] (Box 8, Folder 200)
  - Gurney, Oliver R.(*), 1946-1955 (Box 8, Folder 201-202)
  - Gurney, Oliver R.(*), 1956-1963 (Box 8, Folder 203)
  - Gustavs, Arnold, 1936-1937 (Box 8, Folder 203)
  - Haas, Terry, 1956-1958 (Box 8, Folder 204)
  - Haase, Richard, 1957-1958, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 204)
  - Hackman, [George G.?], undated (Box 8, Folder 204)
  - Hadley, Arthur T., 1962 (Box 8, Folder 204)
  - Hahn, E. Adelaide(*), 1934-1947 (Box 8, Folder 204)
    See also: box 13, folder 338-343
  - Hahn, E. Adelaide(*), 1950-1967 (Box 8, Folder 205)
  - Hahn, Frida (Mrs. G.), 1939 (Box 8, Folder 205)
  - Haines, Richard Carl.(*), 1947, 1955-1966, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 206-207)
  - Haldar, Alfred, 1949-1950 (Box 9, Folder 208)
  - Hale, Mason E., 1958-1959 (Box 9, Folder 208)
  - Hall, Robert A., Jr., 1946 (Box 9, Folder 208)
  - Halle, Fannina, 1941-1942 (Box 9, Folder 208)
  - Halle, H. von, 1934 (Box 9, Folder 208)
  - Hallo, William W., 1956-1967 (Box 9, Folder 209)
  - Hamilton, Charles(*), 1956-1962 (Box 9, Folder 210)
  - Hammerich, Louis L., 1949-1951 (Box 9, Folder 211)
  - Hammond, Philip C., 1955 (Box 9, Folder 211)
  - Hamp, Eric, 1953-1954 (Box 9, Folder 211)
  - Hanfmann, George M.A., 1935, 1937, 1942, 1948-1962 (Box 9, Folder 212)
  - Hansen, Donald P.(*), 1956-1966 (Box 9, Folder 213)
  - Hansen, William H., 1960 (Box 9, Folder 213)
  - Hardy, Robert S., 1948-1952 (Box 9, Folder 214)
  - Harris, Rivkah B.(*), 1954-1965 (Box 9, Folder 214)
  - Harris, Zellig S.(*), 1937-1943 (Box 9, Folder 215)
  - Harris, Zellig S., 1945-1947 (Box 9, Folder 216)
  - Hartmann, Richard, 1926, 1929 (Box 9, Folder 217)
  - Harvard University, Ad Hoc Committee on Middle Eastern Studies, [post-1965] (Box 9, Folder 217)
  - Harvard University, Semitic Museum
    See: box 5, folder 111
  - Harvard University Press, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 218)
  - Hau, Kathleen (Mrs. Hans), 1970 (Box 9, Folder 218)
  - Haugen, Einar, 1944 (Box 9, Folder 218)
  - Hawkins, David, undated (Box 9, Folder 218)
  - Hayden, Roy E., 1962 (Box 9, Folder 218)
  - Hayes, William C., undated (Box 9, Folder 218)
  - Heidel, Alexander, 1945-1946, 1952-1953 (Box 9, Folder 218)
  - Heidelberg, Universität, 1948-1949, 1961-1967 (Box 9, Folder 218)
  - Heidelberger Akademie der Wissenschaften, undated (Box 9, Folder 218)
  - Der Heidelberger Student, 1929 (Box 9, Folder 218)
  - Heinrich, Ernst, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 219)
    See also: box 9, folder 206-207
  - Helck, Wolfgang, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 219)
  - Held, Moshe, 1960-1965 (Box 9, Folder 219)
  - Held, Warren H., Jr.(*), 1954-1963 (Box 9, Folder 220)
  - Henning, Walter B., 1946, 1954-1955 (Box 9, Folder 221)
  - Herbig, Reinhard, 1925, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 221)
  - Herdner, Andrée, 1949-1950 (Box 9, Folder 221)
  - Hermann, Eduard, 1929, 1934, 1936 (Box 9, Folder 221)
  - Herzfeld, Ernst, 1936-1937, undated (Box 9, Folder 221)
  - Herzog, Franz Alfred, 1928 (Box 9, Folder 221)
  - Hessische Landesuniversität, 1933 (Box 9, Folder 221)
  - Highroad, 1950 (Box 9, Folder 221)
  - Hirmer, Max, 1962, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 222)
  - Hirsch, Hans, 1961, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 222)
  - Historia
    See: box 20, folder 530
  - Hitti, Philip K., 1945 (Box 9, Folder 222)
  - Hjelmslev, Louis, 1934-1937 (Box 9, Folder 222)
  - Hoenigswald, Henry, 1951 (Box 9, Folder 222)
  - Hönigswald, Hilde, 1938 (Box 9, Folder 222)
  - Hoffner, Harry A., Jr.(*), 1963-1969 (Box 9, Folder 223)
  - Holborn, Hajo, 1934 (Box 9, Folder 223)
  - Holma, Harry, 1946 (Box 9, Folder 223)
  - Holt, Jens, 1952-1962 (Box 9, Folder 224)
  - Holz, Hellmuth, 1948, 1953-1954 (Box 9, Folder 224)
  - Hommol, Fritz, 1924, 1928 (Box 9, Folder 224)
  - Hone, Margaret E., 1950 (Box 9, Folder 224)
  - Honeyman, Alexander Mackie, 1950 (Box 9, Folder 224)
  - Hopkins, Grace L., 1952 (Box 9, Folder 225)
  - Horn, Siegfried H., 1958 (Box 9, Folder 225)
  - Houghton Mifflin Company, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 225)
  - Hourani, George F., 1959 (Box 9, Folder 225)
  - Howe, Bruce, 1952-1955 (Box 9, Folder 226)
  - Hoyt, Samuel L., 1951 (Box 9, Folder 226)
  - Hrozný, Bedrich(*), 1925-1941, 1946-1947 (Box 9, Folder 227)